cluburb.com 2015-06-14

# Privacy Policy | Hyderabad - Cluburb

  * Tuesday, 03 September 2013 15:58 
  * Category: [General](http://www.cluburb.com/privacy/general)

Our Commitment to Privacy Welcome to ClubUrb.com. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, the terms “ClubUrb”, “this”, “Web Site”, “we”, “us”, “our”, “company” shall mean ClubUrb.com and the terms “user”, “you” refer to you, the user of this Web Site.  
ClubUrb.com takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously. This Privacy Policy outlines how we treat any personal or business information we collect when you visit our Web Site and/or register with us for using special features.  
Personal Information ClubUrb may collect your personal information such as your name, sex, age, e-mail, phone number, address and photos in order to provide you special features such as commenting, sharing or other forms of activity which need user participation.  
ClubUrb does not collect any other personal information that you do not provide on your own. Occasionally, we may share your personal information to notify you about important changes to our Web Site, new services or special offers via e-mail or messages.  
ClubUrb will never sell or share your personal information, including your e-mail address, phone number to any third parties without your express permission.  
Non-Personal Information ClubUrb may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as annual income, buying preferences, or age, also known as demographic and profile data. Though this information is optional, we may use it to improve our Web Site and/or tailor your experience on our Web Site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising in the ClubUrb e-mail or on the Web Site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.  
Disclosure of Information We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of personal information, we have put in place suitable procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on the Web Site.  
You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., username, password, email, phone number) via reviews, comments, or other postings on the Web Site, that information can be collected and used by third parties and could result in unsolicited messages from other users or third parties. Such activities are beyond control of ClubUrb and we assume no responsibility in such circumstances.  
Upon your request, we can provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have the opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.  
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.  
Security It is our intent to keep secure any personal information you submit to us, and we will continue to take steps to maintain the security of our site and your personal information. All user accounts at ClubUrb are password-protected. We restrict the access to your personal information to only authorized personnel.  
While we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosure of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with our Privacy Policy. The open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. Therefore, in submitting your personal information to this Web Site, you assume the risk of a third party obtaining that information.  
You hereby acknowledge that ClubUrb is not responsible for a third party accessing your personal information in such a manner, and you release us from all claims arising out of any use of such information in an unauthorized manner.  
Cookies Like most sites, ClubUrb makes use of browser cookies. Cookies are small text files placed on your computer by our server. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. They allow us to quickly check your status as a user and facilitate access to your preferences. ClubUrb will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services.  
You should be aware that ClubUrb cannot control the use of cookies by advertisers or any information advertisers may gather from their use of cookies. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Web Site.  
Links to Other Sites As part of our services, ClubUrb may create links allowing you to access third-party sites. ClubUrb is not responsible for the content that appears on these sites and does not endorse these sites. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web Site to another Web Site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Please consult the third-party sites’ individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.  
Email & Choice If you do not like any information we send by e-mail regarding new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an option to request no future notices.  
Children Our Site is not intended for the use by minors. We do not knowingly market to, or solicit data from minors.  
Modifications to Privacy Policy By using the Web Site, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy periodically, but the changes will be posted here. So be sure to check in periodically to be aware of any changes to it.  
Contact Us If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.  
Last Updated: 1/1/2008
